diadora.com 2016-12-29

# Diadora: Trainers and Sportswear | Diadora UK

__FREE SHIPPING OVER 49£ __

 __Orders placed between 24th December and 2nd of January might have longer shipping times. __

  1.   2.   3.   4. 

B.ELITE WNT BRIGHT

Extreme protection

B.ELITE SUEDE

The most loved court model in sneakers history

RUNNING

Diadora Running world has always been characterized by constant innovation and research for performance

SHOP NOW

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**DATA CONTROLLER AND DATA PROCESSOR**

As a consequence of the use of this website, personal information concerning identified or identifiable individuals might be processed.   
Zerogrey S.r.l. with registered offices in Via L. Colli, 15 10128 Turin, Italy, tax code and VAT n. 08003340018 e Diadora Sport S.r.l. with registered offices in Caerano di San Marco (TV), Italy, via Montello 80, 31031, tax code and VAT n. 04308510264 are joint Data Controllers.

**PROCESSING OF DATA**

Specific safety measures are in place to prevent loss of data, illegal or improper use and unauthorized access. 

Any processing connected to the services of this website is solely carried out by the staff appointed for data processing purposes or by personnel engaged in maintenance operations. Personal data provided by users forwarding requests of information material is only used to execute the requested service or performance and are only disclosed to third parties if necessary for said purpose.

**TYPE OF DATA PROCESSED**

Browsing Data

The computer systems and software procedures used to operate this website during their normal operation acquire some personal data which transmission is implicit in using the Internet communication protocols.

It is information which is not collected for the purpose of being associated with specific individuals, but which might - due to its nature and through processing and associations with data held by third parties - enable identification of users. 

Included in this category of data there are the IP addresses or the domain names of the computers used by the users connecting to the website, URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) of the requested resources, time of request, method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the response from the server (successful, error, etc.) and other parameters relating to the operating system and the user's computer environment.  
This data is only used to obtain anonymous statistical information on using the website and to check its correct operation.  
Data may be used to ascertain responsibility in case of hypothetical computer crimes against the website: except for this possibility, the data on web contacts do not persist for more than seven days.

Data supplied voluntarily by the user

The optional, explicit and voluntary submission of e-mails to the addresses provided in this website entails the subsequent acquisition of the sender's address, necessary for responding to his requests, and of any other personal data included in the message. Specific summary information dedicated to particular services on request will be provided or displayed on the website pages.

Cookie Policy

Cookies consist of a small amount of data containing information on your visit to websites that can be stored on your computer or other Internet-enabled devices, for instance smartphones and tablets.

We may use cookies to make it easier for you to browse our website, to adapt its contents to your interests and to personalize your experience offering faster access to the website. Cookies simplify and facilitate the interaction between the user and the website, allowing the website to remember the user’s preferences and individual activities, resulting in time-saving and an easier and more efficient browsing. Cookies can memorize information on the website (language, number of visits, font dimension..) and facilitate the supply of several services (user registration, use of the shopping basket, newsletter subscription or products upgrades etc.).

We also use cookies to create aggregate, anonymous statistics, in order to understand how users use our website and to allow us to improve the structure, the content and the services offered on this website.

If a service is not completely anonymized, you will find it listed in the Third party cookies for which you can refuse your consent. 

This website uses three different types of cookies: 

**1\. Essential technical Cookies**

These cookies are strictly necessary session cookies essential to enable a correct and smooth functioning of the website: they allow the browsing, the sharing of on line content, the session authentication and access to secure areas to make your access to the website more rapid and efficient and to maintain your preferences and credentials during the browsing and the shopping experience. Without these cookies, necessary services cannot be provided. 

**2\. Analytic cookies**

These cookies allow us to understand how users use the website and how they move around the e-shop, in order to assess and evaluate its functioning and to create the most appropriate content, tailored on our users’ preferences. For example, these cookies tell us what are the most and the less visited pages, how many users visit the website, how much time a user generally spends on the website and how users arrived on the website. By doing that, we can understand what are the optimal settings and what improvements can be made so that contents can be charged quickly and visualized in an appropriate manner. All data that is collected anonymously by these cookies and is not linked in any way to the user’s personal information. To carry out these actions, on our websites we use third parties services to anonymized collected data. 

**3\. Third Party Tracking Cookies**

These cookies are provided by third parties not controlled and not likely to become controlled by Zerogrey. Therefore, the latter may not provide any guarantee on the use of the information collected by these third party data controllers.   
These third party cookies allow to provide additional information and advanced and personalized functions. Among many features, the possibility to share content through social networks and to enjoy a personalized experience on the basis of the preferences expressed by the users through the pages visited in the past. These services are mainly provided by external operators. Should the user have an account or use the services provided by any third parties providing tracking cookies, these third parties could be able to know whether the user visited our website. The use of data collected by these external operators through the use of tracking cookies is subject to the respective policies regarding personal information that can be found in the links listed below. Any third parties profiling cookies is identifiable by the name of its operator in the list below, and can be disabled by following the instructions stated in the links below.

**Cookies Management**

You can manage your Cookies preferences on your computer or your mobile device through your browser application settings. At any time, you have the option to decline the installation of cookies by third parties and to remove cookies that were previously installed, included those containing your cookies preference settings that you have expressed here. changing your browser application settings. To adjust or change your browser settings you shall consult the instruction manual or the “help” portion of the browser toolbar .

Below are listed the cookies instructions for the main browsers 

Chrome : [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies)

Firefox:[https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Attivare%20e%20disattivare%20i%20cookies?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Attivare%20e%20disattivare%20i%20cookie?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)

Safari: [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=it_IT&locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=it_IT&locale=en_US)

Internet Explorer: <http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies>

Alternatively, to disable all or some specific cookies, you can use the tools provided below. 

Please be aware that disabling cookies that are currently in use may worsen your browsing experience, preventing you to efficiently access to certain parts of the website or personalized information when you visit again the website.

Please remember to set your devices’ browsers with consistency, so that all of them reflect equally your cookies preferences.

Detailed information about cookies functions and cookies acceptance or disablement on the main browsers can be obtained on [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/privacy-policy.htm> . For additional information and assistance on cookies and advertising you can visit the website <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/>

**Cookies list**

Partner | Category | Optout  
---|---|---  
AdRoll  |  Advertising  |  <https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy>  
AppNexus  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy>  
BidSwitch  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.iponweb.com/privacy-policy/>  
Clicky  |  analytics  |  <http://clicky.com/help/custom#sticky_data_disable>  
Criteo  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.criteo.com/deactivate-criteo-banners/>  
DoubleClick  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html>  
Facebook  |  Advertising  |  <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>  
Google Adwords  |  Advertising  |  <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>  
Google Analytics  |  analytics  |  <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
Google+ Platform  |  Social  |  <https://plus.google.com/settings>  
Lijit  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.lijit.com/choices>  
LiveRamp  |  Advertising  |  <http://liveramp.com/opt_out/>  
OpenX  |  Advertising  |  <http://openx.com/legal/>  
Pinterest  |  Social  |  <https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>  
PubMatic  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.pubmatic.com/opt-out.php>  
Right Media  |  Advertising  |  <https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html>  
Twitter  |  Advertising  |  <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405-your-privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads>  
Yieldlab  |  Advertising  |  <http://www.yieldlab.de/kontakt/yieldlab-opt-out/?lang=en>  
  
**Acceptance and disablement of cookies**

By continuing the website browsing after the viewing the short Cookie information notice, by closing the same, by clicking on any part of the homepage or by simply scrolling it to visualize additional content, you accept Zerogrey’s Cookie Policy and the ensuing settings of data collection procedures and the use of cookies. Should you fail to accept the cookies by withdrawal from internet browsing, cookies that have already been stored on your browser will remain registered there but they will not be read nor used until any subsequent and possible acceptance of this Policy. You will always be entitled to remove said cookies, at any time, through the procedures of the aforementioned websites, listed above under the paragraph “Cookies Management” or through the disablement tools provided above.

**Data Processing**

The purposes and procedures of the processing the data are intended for, the exercise of the rights provided by the Legislative Decree 196/2003 (Italian Data Protection Code) and the contact information to exercise those rights are indicated in the Privacy Statement. 

**OPTIONAL NATURE OF PROVISION OF DATA**

Apart from what has already been stated regarding browsing data, the user is free to release personal data when required in special sections of the site. However, failure to supply the aforementioned data may entail the impossibility to receive any of the requested services. 

**USERS RIGHTS**

Users have the right to obtain information on the existence of any recordings of their personal information at any time, and to know the content and origin of personal information, check their correctness or ask for their updating, amendment (article 7 of the Italian Data Protection Code).

Pursuant to the same article, the user has the right to or integration, their cancellation, anonymization or the blocking of any data processed illegally; they also have the right to fight the processing of collected personal information about them, for legitimate reasons. 

In order to exercise these rights, the users can contact the joint Data Controllers: Zerogrey S.r.l. with sole shareholder, with registered offices in Via L. Colli, 15, 10128 Turin, Italy, tax code and VAT n. 08003340018 and Diadora Sport S.r.l. with registered offices in Caerano di San Marco (TV), Italy, via Montello 80, 31031, tax code and VAT n 04308510264. **.**
